EDOARDO DEBENEDETTI

Computer Science M.Sc. Student @ EPFL

dedeswim

■ edoardo.m.debenedetti@gmail.com

in /in/edoardo-debenedetti

I am an M.Sc. in Computer Science student at EPFL, a world-leading university for the subject, willing to focus my studies on Machine Learning and Security. I am a highly curiosity-driven and my goal is to become an ML Research Scientist, after pursuing a Ph.D. in Computer Science.



EDUCATION

EPFL - Federal Institute of Technology Lausanne

M.Sc. in Computer Science | 09/2019 - 07/2021 (expected) Lausanne (CH)

Focus on Machine Learning ad Security.

PoliTo - Turin Polytechnic University

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering | 09/2016 - 07/2019 Turin (IT)

- GPA 28.4/30.
- Graduation mark 110/110, top <8.99%, final year GPA 29.8/30.
- Exchange year at 同济大学 (Tongji University), in Shanghai.

EXPERIENCE

JEToP - PoliTo's Junior Enterprise

International Manager | 10/2018 - 06/2019 Turin (IT)

Executive Board member responsible for public relations and partnerships.

- While I was in charge, JEToP signed 8 new strategic
- Past positions: IT Consultant, Fundraising & Partnership Assistant.

Reply

Intern | 11/2018 - 03/2019 Turin (IT)

Reply is one of the top IT consulting groups in Italy, with a revenue worth €1B+ in 2018.

- Created a chatbot that answers questions about GDPR law.
- Worked on RPA, using Automation Anywhere and Python.

AWARDS

PoliTong Scholarship

Turin Polytechnic University - Tongji University

Given to 11 among 35 students that participated in the selection. It supported a one-year exchange in Shanghai.

PROJECTS

GDPR Chatbot

Reply | 02/2019

A chatbot that answers questions about GDPR.

• Stack: Telegram, TypeScript on Node.js, Redis, MongoDB, IBM Watson Assistant, Docker.

Pindery, an amazing party app

Tongji University | Spring 2018

An open-source, cross-platform application to organize parties, developed in team as a project for the Software Engineering course.

- My team was given the top mark of the class.
- Stack: Flutter, Google Cloud Firestore, TypeScript on Google Cloud Functions.

<> SKILLS

С	Java
TypeScript	Python
Dart	Unix
Flutter	git
MATLAB	SQL
LaTeX	Bash

本 LANGUAGES

Italian Native

Enalish

TOEFL iBT 108/120

French Intermediate





